### **CURRICULUM VITAE**

### AJIBOYE MUIDEEN OLADAYO B.Eng

17, Fayemi street,
Opposite CocaCola Plc,
Mokola,
Ibadan.
ajiboyemuideen23@gmail.com
(+234-8132374077, 8071154961)

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a highly motivated individual with significant experience both in practical roles and in the achievement of academic success. I exhibit keen desire for career progression with a proven record of personal development. I possess the ability to grasp new concepts swiftly and adapt to changing business needs. I am able to manage time effectively whilst prioritizing workload through unrelenting dedication, humility and undiluted passion for excellence. I am a friendly, approachable individual with excellent interpersonal skill.

### **PERSONAL DETAIL**

Date of Birth: October 23, 1993

Gender: Male
Marital Status: Single
Nationality: Nigerian

### **CORE SKILLS**

- Proficient use of MS Office suite: Microsoft Word, Excel.
- Proficient use of AUTOCAD.
- Superior communication skills both written and verbal
- Polite, creative and resourceful.
- Well developed analytical and numerical ability.
- Ability to work unsupervised and meeting up with stipulated deadlines.
- Exceptional multi-tasking and unequal interpersonal skills.

### **ACCOMPLISHMENTS/ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Developed ability to successfully work in a team
- Second best graduating student, department of Mechanical Engineering, University of Ilorin, Nigeria (October, 2015)

### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

### **MECHANICAL ENGINEERING**

AUGUST 2018 TILL APRIL 2022

### DEPARTMENT OF PETROLEUM RESOURCES HEADQUARTERS, LAGOS

### JOB TITLE: MECHANICAL ENGINEER II

- Regulation of white products depots
- Review of depot designs to ensure it meets the department's guideline

- Keeping records of white products' stock
- Coastal vessels inspection
- Clearing vessels importing petroleum products into Nigeria

### **MECHANICAL ENGINEERING**

**APRIL 2022 TILLDATE** 

## NIGERIA MIDSTREAM AND DOWNSTREAM PETROLEUM REGULATORY AUTHORITY JOB TITLE: MECHANICAL ENGINEER I

- Keeping records of white products' stock
- Coastal vessels inspection
- Clearing vessels importing petroleum products into Nigeria

### MAINTENANCE ENGINEER

JUNE 2017 - JULY 2018

## AMO BYNG NIGERIA LIMITED, AWE, OYO JOB TITLE: SENIOR MAINTENANCE OFFICER

- Maintenance and repair of machines
- Planning and supervising maintenance schedule
- Design of machine parts that can be fabricated locally

### LABORATORY TECHNOLOGIST (ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING)

November 2015 – September 2016

## Kano University of Science and Technology, Wudil, Kano JOB TITLE: TECHNOLOGIST

- Conducting practical for students
- Operation of control engineering Laboratory apparatus

### **ENGINEERING TRAINEE**

September 2013 - March 2014

FTN Cocoa processors plc— Gellato bus-stop, Olodo, Ibadan, Oyo State, Nigeria

- JOB TITLE: INTERN
  - Maintenance of Cocoa Presses, Bauermeister, Roaster
  - Repair of cocoa liquor pumps of different ratings
  - Installation of pipes and flanges
  - Partook in the daily maintenance team meeting, deliberation over proficient fault rectification methods to reduce production downtime

### STUDENTS WORK EXPERIENCE PROGRAM

August 2012 – November 2012

**JOB TITLE: INTERN** 

Engineering workshop practices

### **EDUCATION**

**UNIVERSITY OF ILORIN** – Ilorin, Kwara State, Nigeria 2015

**B.Eng** – Mechanical Engineering (First Class Division)

Nov 2010 - Aug

ADE-ROYAL COMPREHENSIVE COLLEGE— Ibadan, Oyo State, Nigeria	Sep 2007 – May
2010	

Senior Secondary Certificate Examination (SSCE)

# **ADE-ROYAL COMPREHENSIVE COLLEGE** – Ibadan, Oyo State, Nigeria Sep 2004 – June 2007

Junior School Certificate Examination (JSCE)

FRAINING & CERTIFICATION	
National Youth Service Corps (NYSC)	2015
Info-Tech training workshop	2015
National Institute of Mechanical Engineers, (NIMECHE), Unilor	in chapter
<ul> <li>Proficiency certificate and graduate member</li> <li>Nigeria Institute of Management (NIM)</li> </ul>	2016
<ul> <li>Project Management professional training</li> </ul>	2016
Skills edge consulting ltd	
Microsoft Office 365 Training	2020
Green Energy Limited	

### REFEREES

Available on request